A Guide to the Mann Page Papers, 1766-1813
John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Library, Colonial Williamsburg Foundation
John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Library, Colonial Williamsburg
Mann Page Papers, 1765-1869.
John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Library, Colonial Williamsburg Foundation
MS 31.8
5 volumes and 504 items.
Mann Page, 1766-1813.
Administrative Information
Access
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Purchase, 1931.
Alternative Form
Also available on microfilm M-1551.
Biographical/Historical Information
Mann Page, Jr. (1766-1813), of Shelly, Gloucester County, Va., was the oldest son of John and Frances Burwell Page.
Scope and Content Information
Papers of Mann Page, Jr. Primarily his business accounts and receipts, and legal papers and receipts relating to his position as clerk of the Gloucester County Court. Included are a few letters pertaining to financial matters at Rosewell, and a letter, August 11, 1787, from John Mason, a student at the College of William and Mary, to Page, stating that there were only five students in the college at the time. A few later accounts were probably kept by Page's descendants.
Arrangement
Chronologically arranged. Undated materials including the five volumes are placed at the end.
Index Terms
Family Names:
Page family.
Persons:
Page, Mann, 1766-1813.
Corporate Names:
College of William and Mary--Students-- History--18th century.
Geographical Names:
Gloucester County (Va.)--Politics and government--18th century.; Rosewell Plantation (Va.)
Contents List
- Virginia Gazette, July 1765. (Folder 1)
  Page from the Virginia Gazette, containing promotions, books published in July and stock prices 27 June to 26 July 1765.
- Bond, Richard Armistead to John McDonall and Co., 15 July 1775., Printed form with manuscript insertions. (Folder 1)
- Account, Richard Armistead to John McDonall and Co., 29 August 1776. (Folder 1)
- Order, Mann Page to the Inspector of [?], May 1778. (Folder 1)
  An order to deliver to Mr. Flicker a note for tobacco.
- Deed, Richard Coleman to John Page, 9 August 1783. (Folder 1)
  Deed for a slave named Tom in Gloucester County.
- Letter fragment, Williamsburg, 6 March 1784. (Folder 1)
  First page of a letter discussing a plan of trade.
- Account, Matthew Anderson for Mr. Page to M. Anderson and Co., November 1786. (Folder 1)
- Receipted account of Mann Page to Gabriel Maupin, 12 November 1786. (Folder 1)
- Receipt, James Wilson [William and Mary steward] to Mann Page, 21 November 1786. (Folder 1)
- John T. Mason, William and Mary, to Mann Page Jr., Rosewell, 11 August 1787. (Folder 1)
- Robert Innes to [?], 31 January 1788. (Folder 2)
  Order to deliver three bushels of wheat to William Lucas, overseer for Mann Page, Timberneck.
- William Harrison to Mann Page, 6 May 1788. (Folder 2)
  Receipt for 1787 taxes.
- Thomas Filchet to Mr. Page, 2 June 1788. (Folder 2)
  Concerns a lawsuit.
- Account of Mann Page, Jr. with Edward Charlton, 4 June 1788. (Folder 2)
- Bill, Edward Charlton to Mann Page, 4 June 1788. (Folder 2)
- James Dawson to Mann Page, Rosewell, 15 July 1788. (Folder 2)
  Request for a loan, receipted 16 July 1788 by Peter Bell.
- John Page to Mann Page 19 October 1788. (Folder 2)
  Letter re getting a doctor for ill slaves. Also mentions Dr. Griffin and Nathaniel Burwell's estate.
- Account, Capt. Samuel Eddins to Thomas Nelson, October 1788. (Folder 2)
- Account, Mann Page, Jr., to Lawrence Gibbons, 17 November 1788. (Folder 2)
- Account, Mann Page to William Cary, 20 November 1788. (Folder 2)
- Elizabeth Teagle to Mann Page, 9 December 1788. (Folder 2)
  Order to let John Spencer have two barrels of corn.
- Lawrence Gibbons to Mann Page Jr., Gloucester County, 15 December 1788. (Folder 2)
  Order for pork.
- Receipt, Lawrence Gibbons to Mann Page, Jr., 31 December 1788. (Folder 2)
- Account, William Lucas to Mann Page, 1 January 1789. (Folder 3)
- Poem fragment, 7 January 1789. (Folder 3)
- Account, Col. John Page and Mann Page to Dedman and Burt, York warehouse, 17 February 1789. (Folder 3)
- Receipted account, Mann Page, Jr., to William Morris, 12 March 1789. (Folder 3)
- Account, Mann Page to the sheriff of Gloucester County, James Bayton, March 1789. (Folder 3)
- Receipt, Mann Page, Jr., to John Carey, 1 April 1789., Printed form with manuscript insertions. (Folder 3)
- Receipt, 1 May 1789. (Folder 3)
  Receipt for a delivery of wheat to Dr. Enis.
- Receipt, Edward Fields to Mann Page, Jr., 2 May 1789. (Folder 3)
- Receipt, Thomas Newman to Mann Page, 7 May 1789. (Folder 3)
- Receipt, Mann Page to Henry Curry, 28 May 1789. (Folder 3)
  Receipt for 1788 poor taxes.
- Receipt, Mathew Pope to Mr. Lucas for Mann Page, Jr., 18 December 1789. (Folder 4)
- Receipt, Mathew Pope to Mann Page, 24 December 1789. (Folder 4)
- Receipt, Lawrence Gibbons to Mann Page, Jr., 24 December 1789. (Folder 4)
- Account, Mann Page to the clerk of Gloucester County, C. Pryor, December 1789. (Folder 4)
- Account, Mann Page, Jr., 1789. (Folder 4)
  Concerns postage.
- Tax account, 1789. (Folder 4)
  Tax account of Mann Page, for 1789. Includes revenue tax, county levy, and poor rates.
- Solicitors accounts, 1789. (Folder 4)
- Account of Col. John Page with Ambrose Anderson, 1 January 1790. (Folder 5)
- Appraisal, 17 January 1790. (Folder 5)
  Appraisal by P. Tabb and D. Cary of two horses of Mann Page and two yoke of oxen of J. Dean.
- Receipt, James Bayton, sheriff to Mann Page Jr., 1 February 1790. (Folder 5)
  Receipt for 1788 taxes.
- Account, Mann Page to the clerk of Gloucester County, C. Pryor, February 1790. (Folder 5)
- Account of Mann Page with Marmaduk Tinkham, 9 March 179[0?] (Folder 5)
- Receipt, William Nelson Jr. to Mann Page, Jr., of Rosewell, 10 March 1790. (Folder 5)
- John Smith to Mann Page, 6 June 1790. (Folder 5)
  Concerns the balance to money received from Mr. Bassett to be paid to Thomas Dixon. Receipt 7 June 1790 by Henry Fox.
- James Macleod, York, to Mann Page, Rosewell, 10 July 1790. (Folder 5)
  Concerns tobacco and the order of various articles.
- James Macleod, York Town to Mann Page, 21 July 1790. (Folder 5)
  Concerns delivery to Page of goods he ordered, a tobacco order, and Burwell's estate.
- Account of Thomas Tabb of Gloucester, 11 August 1790. (Folder 5)
- Bill from John Powell, 21 August 1790. (Folder 5)
- Order, 11 September 1790. (Folder 6)
  Order to Mr. Teagle in favor of Spencer for 2 barrels of corn and 5 bushels of wheat to Ambrose Anderson. 5 bushels of wheat out of last crop to Anderson.
- Ambrose Anderson to Mann Page, 11 September 1790. (Folder 6)
  Order for 5 bushels of wheat.
- Account of Ambrose Anderson with Mann Page, 11 September 1790. (Folder 6)
- Memorandum, 30 September 1790. (Folder 6)
  Concerns a suit for debt. John Perrin vs. Stephen Field, pending in Williamsburg District Court.
- Tax receipt, Frank S. Stubbs, sheriff, to Mann Page, Jr., 6 November 1790. (Folder 6)
  Tax receipt for 1789, county levy and tax rates.
- Tax receipt for 1788. Frank S. Stubbs, sheriff, to Mann Page, Jr., 6 November 1790. (Folder 6)
- Receipt. John [Gwyn?] for Alexander Macauley to John Page, 10 November 1790. (Folder 6)
- Receipt. John [Gwyn?] for Alexander Macauley to William Lucas for Mann Page, 10 November 1790. (Folder 6)
- Receipted account. Mann Page to John Powell, 13 December 1790. (Folder 6)
- Receipt to Mat. Gibs, 22 December 1790. (Folder 6)
- Receipt. John Burcher to Mr. Lucas for Mann Page, 24 December 1790. (Folder 6)
- Robert Greenhow to Mann Page, Rosewell, Gloucester, 29 December 1790. (Folder 6)
  Concerns interest due on loan to Greenhow. Statement included.
- Receipted account of Mann Page with William Cary, 6 January 1791. (Folder 7)
- Receipt from John Burcher to William Lucas, 25 January 1791. (Folder 7)
- Fred W. Hearn to Mann Page, 8 February 1791. (Folder 7)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with Thomas Glass, 8 May 1791. (Folder 7)
- Receipt from E. Lunsford to William Lucas, 10 May 1791. (Folder 7)
- Dudley Cary to Mann Page, 21 May 1791. (Folder 7)
- Receipt from Fran Charlton for John Powell to Mann Page, 4 June 1791. (Folder 7)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with J. Nuttall, 8 June 1791. (Folder 7)
- Tax account of Mann Page for 1790, 4 July 1791. (Folder 7)
- Account of Mann Page with Thomas Glass, 9 July 1791. (Folder 7)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with John Powell, 29 July 1791. (Folder 7)
- Receipt from W. Shackleford to William Lucas, 1 August 1791. (Folder 8)
- Receipt from Jasper Hughes to Mann Page, 2 August 1791. (Folder 8)
  For taxes and poor rate rates for 1790.
- Thomas Hacks, Rosewell, to Mann Page, 1 September 1791. (Folder 8)
- Receipt from Matthew Pope to Mann Page, 26 September 1791. (Folder 8)
- Matthew Pope, York Town, to Mann Page, Gloucester, 30 September 1791. (Folder 8)
- Receipt from Mr. Francis Charlton to Matthew Pope for Mann Page, 25 September 1791. (Folder 8)
- Francis Thorton to Capt. Man[n] Page, 18 October 1791. (Folder 8)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with John Burcher, 21 October 1791. (Folder 8)
- Matthew Pope to Mann Page, 26 October 1791. (Folder 8)
- Receipt from William Morris to William Lucas, 10 November 1791. (Folder 8)
- Bond. Mann Page and William Nelson to William Goosley, 20 December 1791. (Folder 8)
  Receipted 2 March 1792.
- Memorandum, 1791. (Folder 8)
  Concerns William Shermer vs. William Lawson.
- Receipt from Robert Nicholson to Mann Page, 11 January 1792. (Folder 9)
- Receipted account of John Page with J. Pryer, 25 January 1792. (Folder 9)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with John Campbell, 2 March 1792. (Folder 9)
- Memorandum to James Dowson receipt from Mann Page, sum of $5.00, 12 March 1792. (Folder 9)
- Account of Mann Page with Boudon and Pagaud, 17 March 1792. (Folder 9)
- Account, 24 March 1792. (Folder 9)
  Concerns wheat at Scotland, 1791.
- Account of Mann Page with Ambrose Anderson, 2 April 1792. (Folder 9)
- Memorandum, 7 April 1792. (Folder 9)
  Concerns the account of Ambrose Anderson with Mann Page.
- Receipted account of Capt. Wallington with James Dowdall, 14 April 1792. (Folder 9)
- Receipt from Hiram Lankford to Mann Page, 19 April 1792. (Folder 9)
- Receipt, 23 April 1792. (Folder 9)
  Note from F.W. Cook to Mann Page on account of Christopher Pryor.
- Exchange, Mat. Anderson to Mann Page, Rosewell, 28 April 1792. (Folder 9)
- Receipt from John Powell to Mann Page, 1 May 1792. (Folder 10)
  Includes a note from Robert Thruston to Mann Page.
- Receipt. Note from Robert Thruston to Mann Page, 16 May 1792. (Folder 10)
- Account of Mann Page with the clerk of Gloucester, 1 June 1792. (Folder 10)
- Account of Mann Page with Boudon and Pagaud, 8 June 1792. (Folder 10)
- Receipt from Paul Hiling, 8 June 1792. (Folder 10)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with John Moss, 7 August 1792. (Folder 10)
- Receipt from William Fitzhugh, Jr., to Mann Page, Jr., 8 August 1792. (Folder 10)
- Mann Page, Jr., York, to Alice, 14 September 1792. (Folder 10)
- Bond. Mann Page to Alexander Macauley, 15 September 1792., Printed form with manuscript insertions. (Folder 10)
- Louis Pagaud, Gloucester Town, to Mann Page, Jr., 9 November 1792. (Folder 10)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with Robert Nicholson, 23 November 1792. (Folder 10)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with John Campbell, 6 December 1792. (Folder 10)
- Account of Mann Page with Henry Respess, 11 December 1792. (Folder 10)
- Copy of bill of complaint in Chancery Court, [1792] (Folder 10)
  Concerns Nancy and Mary Ayell vs. Benjamin Marable.
- Account of Mann Page with L. Pagaud, 9 January 1793. (Folder 11)
- Account of Mann Page with Drs. Innes and Taylor, 31 January 1793. (Folder 11)
- Receipt from William Lucas to Mann Page, 1 March 1793. (Folder 11)
- Estate account of Dr. John Taylor with Philip Sansum, 6 May 1793. (Folder 11)
- Receipt from David Jameson to Mann Page, Jr., 23 May 1793. (Folder 11)
- Account of Mann Page with the clerk of Gloucester, 1 June 1793. (Folder 11)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with Benjamin Branson, 3 June 1793. (Folder 11)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with sheriff of Gloucester, 2 September 1793. (Folder 11)
- Account of Page with Boudon and Pagaud, 12 September 1793. (Folder 11)
- Bond. Mann Page to Louis Pagaud, 27 September 1793. (Folder 11)
- Receipt. Seymour Harban for Louis Pagaud, 26 November 1793. (Folder 11)
- Receipt from Milton Glassock to Mann Page, 6 January 1794. (Folder 12)
- Receipted account of Page with John Campbell, 6 January 1794. (Folder 12)
- Account of Page with William Reynolds, 17 January 1794. (Folder 12)
- Account of Page with Thomas Whiting, 21 January 1794. (Folder 12)
- Account of Mann Page with John Powell, 1 February 1794. (Folder 12)
- Receipt from John D. Jarvis for a friend. Henry Respess to Mann Page, 11 March 1794. (Folder 12)
- Account of Mann Page with Henry Respess, 11 March 1794. (Folder 12)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with Thomas Whiting, 30 March 1794. (Folder 12)
- Account of Page with Louis Pagaud, 30 April 1794. (Folder 12)
- Account of Page with Philip Sansum, 6 May 1794. (Folder 12)
- Account of Page with Henry Respess, 13 May 1794. (Folder 12)
- Thomas Whiting, Gloster Town, to [Mann Page], 21 June [17]94. (Folder 13)
- Philip Lewis guardian account, 1 July 1794. (Folder 13)
- Thomas Whiting to Mann Page, 9 July 1794. (Folder 13)
- Thomas Whiting to Mann Page, 22 July 1794. (Folder 13)
- Letter to Mann Page, August 1794. (Folder 13)
- Receipt from John Powell to Mann Page, 8 September 1794. (Folder 13)
- Account of John F. Lewis with B. Starke, 23 November 1794. (Folder 13)
- Bond. Simon Laughton to John McDouall and Co., 27 November 1794., Printed form with manuscript insertions. (Folder 13)
- Bond. Thomas Burt, Phillip Burt and Henry Eaton to Benjamin Minor, 27 November 1794. (Folder 13)
- Bond. Mann Page to Richard Leigh, 5 January 1795. (Folder 14)
  Receipted 23 September 1796.
- Account with Captain Tinkhorn, 7 February 1795. (Folder 14)
- Receipt from Louis Pagaud to Mann Page, 5 March 1795. (Folder 14)
- Bill to Mann Page, 24 March 1795. (Folder 14)
- Receipted account of Page with Peter Kemp, 26 March 1795. (Folder 14)
- Bond. Elizabeth Whiting, Peter Whiting and Lewis Burwell to William Nelson Jr., executor of Thomas Nelson, 16 April 1795. (Folder 14)
- Receipted account of Page with Thomas Newman, 27 April 1795. (Folder 14)
- Account of Page with Thomas Whiting, 27 May 1795. (Folder 14)
- William Russell, Williamsburg, to Mann Page, Jr., 6 July 1795. (Folder 15)
- Matthew Anderson to Mann Page, 12 July 1795. (Folder 15)
- Hugh Nelson to Mann Page, 28 July 1795. (Folder 15)
- Mildred Minor to Mann Page, 9 September 1795. (Folder 15)
- Note from Henry Charles and William Charles to Henry Hubbard, 30 October 1795. (Folder 15)
- Will Churchill to Mann Page, 1 November 1795. (Folder 15)
- Receipt. William Pipen to Mann Page, 14 November 1795. (Folder 15)
- Receipted account of Page with John Powell, 2 May 1796. (Folder 16)
- Account of Barley with James Heywood, 14 July 1796. (Folder 16)
- Account signed by Henry Curry, 20 July 1796. (Folder 16)
- Henry Curry to Mann Page, 20 July 1796. (Folder 16)
- Bond. Mann Page and Thomas Nelson to Thomas Fox, executor of William Marshall, 11 August 1796., Printed form with manuscript insertions. (Folder 16)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with Edward Fields, 15 October 1796. (Folder 16)
- Receipt from R. West to Mann Page, 19 October 1796. (Folder 16)
- Account of Page with Thomas Dawson, October 1796. (Folder 16)
- Henry Hughes to Mann Page, 1 November 1796. (Folder 16)
- Account of Page with Thomas Rickard, November 1796. (Folder 16)
- Boswell [?] to Mann Page, [1796] (Folder 16)
- Memorandum, February 1797. (Folder 17)
  Concerns fees due Mann Page in Matthews County.
- Bond. Robert Innes to Benjamin C. Waller, 4 March 1797. (Folder 17)
- Account of Page with Davis, 11 March 1797. (Folder 17)
- Copy of judgement, March 1797. (Folder 17)
  Concerns Warren Hall vs. Thomas Booth.
- A. Kevan to Mann Page, 7 April 1797. (Folder 17)
- Account, 27 May 1797. (Folder 17)
- Account of Man Paige with John Lingan, 29 May 1797. (Folder 17)
- Receipted account of Robert Thurston with W. Rogers, 15 July 1797. (Folder 17)
- Account of Mann Page with Sarah Plummer, September 1797. (Folder 18)
- Petition docket, September 1797. (Folder 18)
- Account of Page with Thomas Newman, 5 December 1797. (Folder 18)
- John Page, Richmond, to Mann Page, Gloucester, 10 December 1797. (Folder 18)
- Receipted order of Richard Leigh on Mann Page, 10 December 1797. (Folder 18)
- The executor of Edward Anderson and Ambrose merchant in account with Mann Page, 1797. (Folder 18)
- Respess and Jarvis in account with Mann Page, 1797. (Folder 18)
- Memorandum, 1797. (Folder 18)
- Thomas Lee Shippan, Indian Queen, to Mann Page, 8 October [179?] (Folder 19)
- Holder Hudgins to Capt. Page, 13 January 1798. (Folder 19)
- James Davis to Mann Page, 22 January 1798. (Folder 19)
- Receipted account of Page with William Rogers, 6 February 1798. (Folder 19)
- McCarty Fitzhugh to Mann Page, 27 February 1798. (Folder 19)
- Account of Law. Gibbons with Thomas Smith, 26 April 1798. (Folder 19)
- Matthews docket, April 1798. (Folder 19)
- Receipted account of Page with Wm. Filchett, 21 May 1798. (Folder 19)
- Memorandum, 27 May 1798. (Folder 19)
- Receipted account of Page with Henry Curry, 2 July 1798. (Folder 19)
- Note from Anthony Bryan to Cornelius Buck and Co., 19 September 1798. (Folder 19)
- Receipted account of Page with Charles Grymes, 31 December 1798. (Folder 19)
- Account of Mann Page with J. Anderson, 13 February 1799. (Folder 20)
- Receipted account of Page with William Reynolds, 23 February 1799. (Folder 20)
- Receipted account of Page with William Cary, 22 April 1799. (Folder 20)
- Receipt from William Morgan to Mann Page, 28 May 1799. (Folder 20)
- Receipted account of Page with Matthews County Court, May 1799. (Folder 20)
- John Anderson in account with Mann Page, May 1799. (Folder 20)
- Receipt from John Sewell to Mann Page, 4 June 1799. (Folder 20)
- Memorandum. T. Jones, 19 June 1799. (Folder 20)
- Vincent Hudson to Mann Page, 23 June 1799. (Folder 20)
- Account of Wm. Morgan to Mann Page, 28 June 1799. (Folder 20)
- William Cary, York to Mann Page, Scotland, 28 June 1799. (Folder 20)
- Mann Page, Jr., to the High Sheriff of Gloucester, 29 June 1799. (Folder 20)
- Receipt from William Morgan to Mann Page, 5 July 1799. (Folder 21)
- Note from Henry Respess to Mann Page, 8 July 1799. (Folder 21)
- William Vaughn, Norfolk to Mann Page, 29 July 1799. (Folder 21)
- Receipt from William Cary to Mann Page, 3 August 1799. (Folder 21)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with Alexander Cowan, 31 August 1799. (Folder 21)
- Receipt from William Reynolds to Mann Page, 21 November 1799. (Folder 21)
- Respess to Mann Page, 1799. (Folder 21)
- Letter to Captain Page, ca. 1799. (Folder 21)
- Memorandum, ca. 1799. (Folder 21)
- Receipt from H. Gale to Mann Page, 15 April 1800. (Folder 22)
- Account of Thomas Rickard with B. Higgins, 18 May 1800. (Folder 22)
- Receipt from William Thornton to Mann Page, 22 May 1800. (Folder 22)
- Mann Page's account, May 1800. (Folder 22)
- Judgement. Lewis B. Whiting, June 1800. (Folder 22)
- Mann Page, Jr., Shellie, to Captain Peter B. Whiting, 26 July 1800. (Folder 22)
- Account of Mann Page, 1 August 1800. (Folder 22)
- Peter B. Whiting to Mann Page, 2 August 1800. (Folder 22)
- Robert Andrews, Williamsburg, to Mann Page, Gloucester, 30 November 1800. (Folder 22)
- Receipt from William Morgan to Mann Page, Jr., 20 December 1800. (Folder 22)
- Warrant, 28 January 1801. (Folder 23)
  Concerns Bracken v. Haywood.
- Copy of James Haywood's account, January 1801. (Folder 23)
- Notice. Mills executors Laughan, 10 March 1801. (Folder 23)
- Account of Page with Richard Minor, 6 April 1801. (Folder 23)
- Memorandum, 1 May 1801. (Folder 23)
- Receipt of notes Mann Page, Jr., 11 May 1801. (Folder 23)
- Copy of judgement, June 1801. (Folder 23)
  Concerns Atkinson v. Lewis Burwell etc.
- Account of Page with the clerk of Gloucester, June 1801. (Folder 23)
- William Filchett to Mann Page, 6 July 1801. (Folder 23)
- Copy of judgement, July 1801. (Folder 23)
  Concerns Thornton v. Fleming etc.
- Affidavit of F. W. Cook re. John Lewis, 4 October 1801. (Folder 23)
- William A. Wynne to Gawin L. Corbin, 6 November 1801. (Folder 23)
- Matthew's memo, November 1801. (Folder 23)
- Issues and writs of inquiry, November 1801. (Folder 23)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with clerk of Gloucester, 1801. (Folder 23)
- Receipt from James Evans to Mann Page, 7 January 1802. (Folder 24)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with Thomas Archer, 13 February 1802. (Folder 24)
- Receipt from Matthew Anderson, 5 April 1802. (Folder 24)
- Judgement, 14 May 1802. (Folder 24)
  Concerns case of Caroline Lewis v. William Nelson & John Wickman.
- Receipted account of Mann Page with Thomas Sewell, 24 June 1802. (Folder 24)
- Account of Mann Page with Richard Minor, 9 July 1802. (Folder 24)
- Account of John Page with J. Samuel, 17 September 1802. (Folder 24)
- Account of Mann Page with Thomas Archer, 25 September 1802. (Folder 24)
- Account of Mann Page with J. Samuel, 14 October 1802. (Folder 24)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with Thomas Archer, 2 November 1802. (Folder 24)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with A. Tufts, 9 November 1802. (Folder 24)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with Alexander Cowan, 4 December 1802. (Folder 24)
- Receipted account of Page with Thomas Archer, 10 January 1803. (Folder 25)
- Account of John Sinclair to the sheriff of Middlesex, April 1803. (Folder 25)
- Account of John Sinclair with the sheriff of Gloucester, May 1803. (Folder 25)
- Order from Henry Wright to Mann Page, 4 July 1803. (Folder 25)
- Walkers Deviesse V. Semple & Slater etc. V. Griffin etc., July 1803. (Folder 25)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with Alexander Cowan, 16 September 1803. (Folder 25)
- Mann Page, Williamsburg, to William Minor, Shellie, 17 September 1803. (Folder 25)
- Account of Joseph Knight with David Banks, 24 September 1803. (Folder 25)
- Poem, 26 September 1803. (Folder 25)
- Receipt from William M. Dennis to Mann Page, 30 September 1803. (Folder 25)
- Receipt from P. Smith to Mann Page, 10 November 1803. (Folder 25)
- Mann Page to William Minor, Shellie, 28 November 1803. (Folder 25)
- Mann Page to William Minor, Shellie, 3 December 1803. (Folder 25)
- Receipted account of Mann Page to Robert Greenhow, 24 December 1803. (Folder 25)
- Account of John Sinclair with the sheriff of Gloucester, 1803. (Folder 25)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with the post office, 16 March 1804. (Folder 26)
- Receipted account of Page with John Wright, 28 March 1804. (Folder 26)
- Account of Mordecai Cook with the clerk of Gloucester County, March 1804. (Folder 26)
- Peter B. Deneufville to Mann Page, 5 May 1804. (Folder 26)
- Account of Mordecai Cook Hayes to the clerk of Gloucester County, May 1804. (Folder 26)
- Account of John F. Lewis to the clerk of Gloucester County, June 1804. (Folder 26)
- Account of William Williams to the clerk of Gloucester County, June 1804. (Folder 26)
- John Sinclair to the sheriff of Gloucester County, June 1804. (Folder 26)
- Receipt from Joseph Monnet to Arthur Davis, 28 July 1804. (Folder 26)
- Account of Benjamin Hope to the clerk of Gloucester County, July 1804. (Folder 26)
- John Miller to the clerk of Gloucester County, July 1804. (Folder 26)
- Mordecai Cook to the sheriff of Gloucester County, July 1804. (Folder 26)
- John Sinclair to the sheriff of Gloucester County, August 1804. (Folder 27)
- John Sinclair to James Van Bebber, August 1804. (Folder 27)
- Causes for trial, August 1804. (Folder 27)
- William Williams to the clerk of Gloucester County, September 1804. (Folder 27)
- Receipt from Jesse Hudejins to Mann Page, 13 November 1804. (Folder 27)
- Receipt from Thomas Stubblefield to Mann Page, 14 November 1804. (Folder 27)